# Mohd Kamil

466, Duatai Garhmukteshwar Hapur UP 245205

kamiliqbal28@gmail.com

Contact no: 8476992882

### **OVERVIEW:-**

With this letter, I would like to express my sincere interest in the Merchandiser position you have available. As a skilled and successful professional with comprehensive merchandising experience within the industry, I possess a wide range of knowledge and experience that will allow me to contribute toward the success of company. Kindly give a chance to serve you.

Thanks!

**WORK EXPERIENCE:-** : WORKED WIRH.

Organization : Shiva Kumar Civil Work Contractor,
Designation : Accounts Clerk Cum Computer Operator

Duration : June 2019-March 2021

Profile : Accounting and Billing Work

Organization : GHF Technologies Pvt.Ltd,

Designation : Supervisor

Duration : May 2018- March 2019.

Profile : Handle company team i/c overall responsibility.

Organization : GHF Technologies Pvt.Ltd,

Designation : Computer Operator
Duration : July 2016-May 2017.

Profile : Typing work

### **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS:-**

#### **▶** B. Com.

Waseem Turki Muslim Degree College, Fatehpur mafi, Palaula J.P Nagar, (M.J.P.R.U.Bareilly) 2017-2019.

# > 12<sup>th</sup> education

UP Board- M.I.U.Inter College Dautai Hapur Utter Pradesh 2013-2014

# > 10<sup>th</sup> education

UP Board- M.I.U.Inter College Dautai Hapur Utter Pradesh 2011-2012.

### PROFESSIONAL KNOWLEDGE:-

### > CABA – MDTP

A-1 S.M.D. Institute Of Information Technology.( NIELIT)

### > C.C.C

A-1 S.M.D. Institute Of Information Technology. (NIELIT)

<u>IT EXPOSURE</u>:- Gmail, Adobe reader, MS Excel, MS Power point, MS Word, Convert file to PDF,

PNG, Online Convert, Paint.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION:-

Father's Name : Mohd Iqbal Khan , Date of Birth : 01-January-1997

Gender : Male

Marital status : Unmarried
Nationality : Indian
Religion : Muslim

( MOHD KAMIL)